{
    "subject": "resource/Dennis_W._Sciama",
    "predicate": "ontology/deathPlace",
    "object": "resource/UK",
    "human_readable": "Dennis W. Sciama died in the UK.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8449164628982544,
            "question": "Was Dennis W. Sciama British?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8271452784538269,
            "question": "Where did Dennis W. Sciama die?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7986574769020081,
            "question": "When did Dennis W. Sciama die?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42794784903526306,
            "question": "What was Dennis W. Sciama known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.38128483295440674,
            "question": "What country was Dennis W. Sciama associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.27763786911964417,
            "question": "Who were some of Dennis W. Sciama's contemporaries?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2640731632709503,
            "question": "What was the significance of Dennis W. Sciama's work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.254369854927063,
            "question": "Where did Dennis W. Sciama conduct his research?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.250479131937027,
            "question": "In what field did Dennis W. Sciama work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22351863980293274,
            "question": "Did Dennis W. Sciama make any notable contributions to science?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Dennis W. Sciama died in the UK.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1095_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what field did Dennis W. Sciama work?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1095_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where did Dennis W. Sciama conduct his research?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1095_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What was the significance of Dennis W. Sciama's work?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1095_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1095_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1095_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1095_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1095_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1095_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1095_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1095_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1095_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1095_79.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1095_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have more triples to evaluate!  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n`{ \"output\": \"no\" }`\n\nThe reason for this answer is that the documents mention Dennis William Siahou Sciama's date of death as 18 December 1999, but do not specify that it occurred in the UK. They only mention his nationality as British, which does not necessarily imply that he died within the country."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement that Dennis W. Sciama died on December 18, 1999, which is in the UK based on historical context and given that he was a British physicist with strong ties to institutions in the UK such as Cambridge and Oxford."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "There is no information in the provided context to confirm Dennis W. Sciama's death location as the UK, whereas his birth place and academic background are mentioned.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}